// Array containing all questions with their corresponding answers and correct answer

const quizBank = [
  {
    question: "Who is the Captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
    answers: [
      "Monkey D. Luffy",
      "Buggy The Clown",
      "Red-Haired Shanks",
      "Edward D. Teach",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Monkey D. Luffy",
  },
  {
    question: "What was Straw Hat Luffy's first bounty?",
    answers: ["30,000 Beli", "15,000 Beli", "50,000 Beli", "20,000 Beli"],
    correctAnswer: "30,000 Beli",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the devil fruit that Straw Hat Luffy ate?",
    answers: [
      "Gomu Gomu no Mi",
      "Mera Mera no Mi",
      "Ope Ope no Mi",
      "Suna Suna no Mi",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Gomu Gomu no Mi",
  },
  {
    question: 'Who said: "Scars on the back are a swordsman\'s shame"?',
    answers: [
      "Dracule Mihawk",
      "Roronoa Zoro",
      "Trafalgar D. Water Law",
      "Axe-Hand Morgan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Roronoa Zoro",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Luffy was faced with anger from which crew member when he made his annoucement about parting with the Going Merry",
    answers: ["Chopper", "Sanji", "Nami", "Usopp"],
    correctAnswer: "Usopp",
  },
  {
    question: '"Iron Pirate" Franky had the original name of what?',
    answers: ["Pandaman", "Mountain Ricky", "Cutty Flam", "Iceberg"],
    correctAnswer: "Cutty Flam",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who assisted Straw Hat Luffy in infiltrating the underwater prison Impel Down?",
    answers: [
      "Boa Hancock",
      "Silvers Raleigh",
      "Donquiote Doflamingo",
      "Kizaru",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Boa Hancock",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Pirate "Fire-Fist" Ace is the commander of which division of the Whitebeard Pirates?',
    answers: ["1st", "2nd", "3rd", "4th"],
    correctAnswer: "2nd",
  },
  {
    question: "In the anime, Gol D. Roger was executed in which way?",
    answers: [
      "Stabbed with two spears",
      "Hung from the gallows",
      "Walked a plank",
      "Decapitated",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stabbed with two spears",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which member of the Straw Hat Pirates was the only one to have their bounty picture drawn?",
    answers: ["Zoro", "Robin", "Brook", "Sanji"],
    correctAnswer: "Sanji",
  },
];
